AHMAD BAYRAKDAR

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

ahmadbayrakdar.github.io

Ahmad.berkdar.sy@gmail.com (+971) 553879113 Damascus, Syria



Full Stack Web Developer & Designer with +7 years of experience. Proficient at React.js, ASP.Net, Node.js, Django, and Python.

I have developed many E-commerce, PWA and SPA sites for many companies in UAE, Qatar, Germany, Egypt, Syria and Lebanon.

Programming is my real passion.

Programming Languages

React Js
Asp.net - Node - Django - Python
SQL - PostgreSQL - Oracle - MongoDB

Soft Skills

Problem Solving - Critical Thinking - Decision Making -Communication

EXPERIENCE

Feb 2023 -Sep 2023

Full Stack Developer and Designer, Proitx - UAE

- Created Integrated Coaching Appointment System (Ranem Yatakan)
- Modern Company Landing Pages with GSAP (BigMedia)
- Backend and UI for Medical Encyclopedia (DmedLab)
- Dashboard Backend and UI for it (DmedLab Dashboard)
- Built the company's new website (proitx.com)

Apr 2022 – Jan 2023

Full Stack Developer, Evntoo - Egypt

• E-Learning and E-Reservation systems:

sna-academy.com afaq-lms.com evntoo.com

Oct 2021 – Apr 2022

Full Stack Developer, Elmalek Furniture - Egypt

• Rebuilt the whole website in WordPress:

elmalekfurniture.com

• Worked with CEO, and Data Analyst to enhance accessibility and UX

May 2021 – Oct 2021	 Full Stack Developer, Qatar Othentic - Qatar Built a Management System for warehouses of the company
Sep 2020 – May 2021	Full Stack Developer, Proitx - Lebanon Developed Websites and built Land Pages for Business Companie Built System for Sign Language Translation with ASP Built System to manage data for clothing company with Python Fixed websites issues with PHP and Laravel Built Ai - Face Recognition System - for automated Ads Built the company website: proix.com
May 2019 – Sep 2020	 Full Stack Developer, Yes-Soft - Germany Built WordPress themes from scratch using HTML, CSS, and PHP. Uploaded and Deployed the WordPress themes. UX for the company system (Yes-Soft)

EDUCATION

Feb 2015 – Mar 2021	Bachelor Degree of Computer Engineering, International University for
	Science and Technology - Damascus
Wiai 2021	The top student in all programming classes with A grades.

Volunteering

Jun 2018 – Nov 2019	Researcher (Information Technology), SYR-RES - Egypt Contributed with my team members to deliver various IT topics.
Sep 2014 – Jan 2015	Team Leader (Class Notes), <i>RBCs – Syria</i> Organized a team of fresh students to write class notes and paper work

AWARDS

2013	· 9 [™] PLACE IN C++ OLYMPICS
2015	· SCHOLARSHIP OF BACHELOR'S DEGREE
2016	· 4 ^{TH PLACE} IN WRO-SYRIA COMPETITION
2017	· 5 TH PLACE IN WRO-SYRIA COMPETITION
2020	· Participating in NACD Exhibition - Ai & ML